Wait to eat a snack.
Wait to eat snack.
Yes, that's good.
How is it?
It's good.
Yes. Wait, wait, wait.
Let me in.
Hello, hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
Hello, everyone. Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Yoo-hoo. Yoo-hoo.
Hi. - Hi.
Hello.
Hello, everybody.
Good afternoon.
So...
I
celebrated my 21st birthday!
Yay!
Today, May 28th, I turned 21!
Oh man, I have stupid hair!
Happy birthday!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
In honor of my birthday.
I'm going to do a lot of live streaming today.
First of all, I'm going to do a youtube live stream by myself.
It's been a while since you've done one by yourself? Have you done it before?
Maybe I have, I don't know.
So I hope you guys are watching.
Congratulations. Thank you. Can we do it this way? I think I'd rather see the comments over here.
Wow, congratulations. Thank you.
Thank you. Thanks for watching.
I'm already 21.
Don't you get injected on your birthday? I do,
I didn't do the camera machine myself today,
Do you want to put it on?
Well, today, you know.
I had a different shoot, so I had a different haircut.
I didn't do anything by myself.
Oh, I'll put that on. Wait a minute.
Can I put this on?
I'm going to put on a special kachinsha.
Wait a minute.
Ta-da!
I'm going to wear this special catsuit today.
Does it say "Made in Japan" or "Made in Clothing"?
There's only one of these in the world... and it's cute... and prettier... and prettier, and prettier... and prettier... and prettier.
I like this one better... but it's not the new one...
It's the only one of its kind in the world, because I love catsuits.
But this one is cuter.
Maybe I'll wear this one around my neck.
I'll put it here.
It's so stylish.
But I have a lot of deliveries, so I'll just use a different one.
What? What do we do? Which one do you guys like better?
This one or this one?
Yes, I love catsuits.
I have a lot of them.
What do you think?
If they were on sale, would you have bought one? This one.
Thank you for watching!
Kihara, you make me want to kneel.
Yes, I recently did a live vocal performance.
I said "Kneel down in Hokkaido" and got a nice cheer!
Like this.
How's it going?
What do you think?
I love catsuits. May I introduce you?
I mean, I don't care if it's a hair arrangement, or if it's a hair accent, or if it's a hair arrangement, or a hair accent...
I love hair arrangements and hair accents.
I love it.
I have some with me right now. I'm going to be doing a lot of deliveries today, so I thought it would be good to have some for now.
I've selected a few things and brought them with me. I still have a lot at home.
Can I introduce them to you? Okay, first of all...
I recently bought something I like.
I hope you like it.
This one. I use it to put my hair up in a half-up.
And...
I don't have a big-sleeved hair band. I don't have a big-sleeved hair band.
And this one. Isn't it cute? I love ribbons, too.
Look at this one.
I love ribbons and sparkles, but we also have this kind of bandage.
This one, too.
Thank you for coming. I was just introducing hair accessories.
My first hair accessory at the age of 21.
My current hair accessory.
This one has ribbons. I love ribbons.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's the same color as before.
I haven't put it on social media yet.
Please check back in the future to see if this will be on there.
How many do you have? I still have some at home.
And then...
I also have these Maticky catsuits.
I like yellow, pink, black
are my favorite colors.
Congratulations, Minneka!Congratulations, Minneka. Thank you.
This is...
It's like a barrette, but it's not a catsuit.
You might think they're the same, but they're different sizes, shapes and textures.
Barrette.
I love ribbons, so I have a few more just like this one at home.
There's a lot more, but I can't show you all of them.
There's these little chouches, and there's these little peas.
You know...
I don't know... I can't go on.
I can't introduce them all, so please visit my Instagram page for more information!
Please visit my instagram
You can see my hair arrangements and
and hair works.
I hope you will pay close attention to my hair arrangements and hair works.
And I'll tell you what else...
I'm screwed!
I'm going to have a lot of fun arranging hair at the age of 21.
That's one of my goals.
(rustling)
Ten minutes late. Safe and sound.
I'm not wearing nail polish right now.
I've gone back to wearing baby nails.
Yeah, but I'm usually a big fan of flashy nails.
I haven't been wearing rings much lately.
I've been going to thrift stores lately, and I've noticed that I'm not wearing clothes when I go to thrift stores.
When I go to thrift stores, I always buy accessories instead of clothes.
I was told that these were imported from the U.S.
I often buy things like this and small sunglasses.
I've also bought a catsuit before.
It's cute, isn't it?
Like a key to a bathhouse, a sauna key, a coin-operated locker key...
It's so cute!
I bought it.
I'm 21, and for my birthday...
For my birthday present...
I want to buy a lot of clothes!
Today's outfit is also from Newdis.
Isn't it cute? Look at this!
Look at those sparkling eyes!
It's a little bit in, but the bottom line is cute too.
I love the episode where the other members had their hair done by Relay.
But everyone's getting better at it these days.
You know...
I'd like to see less of my theme area.
I want to be a dream with sparkling eyes like this.
Mon-chan's here. Thank you.
Yesterday's soccer-uniform outfit was cute, too.
I got it because I thought it was cute.
Thank you for watching!
Happy Birthday and may it be a wonderful one. Thank you.
I took the wrong train. Let's go back.
It's too bad you can't see me in that cute outfit, but I can't just stream it like this.
It can't be helped.
You should get it done sometime.
It's better if I do it myself.
It's a lively crowd today.
Does it match Pealla?
Yes, it's blue.
It's gray.
What's your sister's favorite color?
But it's more Korean.
I always keep an eye on Korea.
Korea.
I like Kate.
She's a bit of a catcher.
Everyone is so curious about what's going on around them.
There's so many of them.
I'm trying to be quiet, but I'm not.
Now, when this switches to the exterior wall.
We'll be in big trouble.
The store will be closed.
I can't run the store.
I'll take care of it and leave the city.
The staff has taken measures to help me
They're so kind
Don't worry about it.
Now, you know, it's picture time
Yes, to the kind staff
So far
We've grown so much.
Thank you very much.
Hi, I'm late.
It's okay. It's okay.
Thank you all for coming.
I haven't really decided what I'm going to do.
I'm going to try to deliver it in a relaxed manner.
It's my birthday too!
Happy Birthday!
Happy Birthday, Kan-chan!
Happy birthday to you!
We are the same
May 28th
Everyone says congratulations.
Congratulations!
Thank you for the conversation view. People say it makes them sleepy.
They say I get sleepy when I talk alone.
Oh...
Fuji is watching us.
Where is he? Mt. Fuji.Where are they? Mt. Fuji
Is he close by?
Come here.
If he's around, come here.
I celebrated yesterday and I'm hungover.
I didn't just have fun.
Is this thing weird? I said it's a little peculiar.
I've got one too.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Are you okay?
I'm not in the other StarPlaza group.
But Airi Tsurumaru gave me a line... and she's always on line with me.
Tsurumaru Airi, one of the Fasic Girls from Stirulast in Sendai.
She's been sending me a lot of messages.
Today, too.
Around midnight, she said congratulations.
She sent me a line saying congratulations.
She messaged me at around midnight to congratulate me.
He made me his icon.
I put it on my Instagram.
I put on my Instagram.
An gave it to the new guy. You like caramel, right?
I love them. -The new guy gave them to me.
I'll do a report on it. I'll try it after I'm done with Ari.
I'll try some after we're done talking about Ari.
She told me that she's always admired me and that she sometimes has problems with me...
She's a very nice girl.
And she has a cheerful personality. I took a workshop with her once.
She's a very cheerful and fun girl.
She's a fun girl, but she's Ijin-san.
So...
Everyone, please take good care of Tsurumaru Irie.
I have a folder with all the photos we took together.
She's so cute.
I'm sure we'll talk about it.
I've been meaning to tell you about this... today...
I'm going to eat the caramel Shinjiya gave me.
It's okay. Here.
I'll eat it.
It's good.
It's good?
Yes, you want some?
Yeah. You sure?
What does it taste like?
You can get out if you want.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry to bother you.
You want to put this on?
Hi. - Hi.
May I?
Is this special?
Yes, it's special.
It matches your clothes. You're right. Today I was going to wear the T-shirt I got for Rine's birthday.
But I didn't get it yet, so I didn't wear it. Next time I'll wear it to the championship.
But I sent that birthday message to Rine.
I was taking a bath and was about half an hour late sending it, which I really regretted.
Don't worry, it's still my birthday, so I forgot to send it again before all the birthdays in May, and I'm pretty sure it's the last one.
I've been into wishing people happy birthday lately, so I sent out a voice message from Shinjuku yesterday wishing them happy birthday, so I sent back a voice message saying thank you.
Oh, and now you want me to play it? Do you want me to play it?
I'll play it then... our record... our record of lovemaking.
Love records of Lineage's Love records of Lineage's Love records of Lineage's Love records of Lineage's Love records of Lineage's
I wonder where it is.
Okay, I'll play it.
Tiki Panama.
Are you getting big?
I'm gonna play it again. I'm gonna pull my voice.
I got a congratulations coming in.
Thank you.
You're so cute.
Did you hear that?
I told you, there's a girl who had the same birthday as me.
I'll send a message from Shinchu.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday!
Thank you
A message from the girl
You can play the voice message, too.
Yunayan... Yunayan said congratulations to Tiffany...
I'll make you a one-of-a-kind forfeit gift...
What's this? It's the only one of its kind in the world!
I've heard that they're trying to make this into a product.
I can't deny that it looks like it's made in a 100-yen store!
I'll give it to you!
Then...
I don't remember anything! What if it's something weird?
Good night for the first stage of Halloween!
I can't remember what to say...
It's getting worse.
What is it? I'm really not drunk.
Hey, hey, it's only 21 seconds.
Oh, my God! I might be a genius!
Yes, I got a 21-second voice message, but I thought for sure Yuna wouldn't do something so naughty.
Oh no! She might be a genius!
I was so happy to get this 21-second voice message.
It's a late-night tension.
I'm like this even if it's not late at night.
It's always like this.It happens all the time.
You know.
People don't know much about it, surprisingly.
I think Yuna is a pretty serious person.
Oh, here they come.
Don't put your face on.
He's more gorgeous than he is.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's personal.
Personal effects?
That thing.
Oh, that's a little peculiar.
I'll let you wear something cute, too.
Okay, I'll get you one from a hundred bucks.
No, no, no.
It's okay, it's only 100 yen.
Thank you. It's really cute.
Let's put this on then.
It's kind of Alice-like.
It's cute. Smell it.
I can smell it.
I just discovered something new.
I can't do it.
You guys are all going to be Linnaeus during the month of Linnaeus, right?
I'll do it.
Which one do you like? This one?
I'll go with the one that hasn't been used a lot by Rinne yet.
Is that okay?
Oh, no.
Are you sure?
What kind of cake are you going to eat?
I like shortcake.
Shortcake? Strawberry shortcake?
Yes, strawberry shortcake.
I don't see anything.
It looks like something.
I'm sorry.
Something's wrong.
I'm getting some kind of beam.
Oh, it's working. It's working.
This way!
Sha!
I like it.
Now I'm getting cute with my nails.
Now everyone's clawing at each other.
Sad.
Are you the type to eat the strawberries last?
First.
Last. Last.
First?
If it's a shortcake, do you take the strawberry first?
Yes, for sure.
Otherwise, you can't eat the cake.
Well, there are many opinions.
Yes, I do.
Thank you.
Lots of accessorizing.
Oh, no, no, no, I messed up Kiwanis' hair.
He said, "Which one of you is the real Renee?
It's me. I'm Riné.
So many songs.
Hello!
Linée in the middle cutting
I am Linée
Hello.
- Please say it. Please say it.
- My name is Linen.
- My name is Ichigo.
- We are all Koreans.
- They're all Koreans.
Grandpa had this on TV.
What? No, right?
No, right?
Come on.
Your comment's gone.
Come back.
Linea, Poco Poco Poco! Do you love me?
It says "lots of Linea"... lots of Linea... lots of Linea...
I want to see you, Pokoshippo!
Pokoshippo, Pokoshippo, Pokoshippo...
Pokoshippo, there are many students of mine... many students...
Fujitani, Yoshise, Yasumori, what should we do?
Please, tell me something... but I can't remember that you're the one who talks like that...
I can't remember... I can't remember...
I want to know... what do you call ramen? Spicy ramen?
Ramyong. Ramyong? Ramyong. That's really good. Ramyong.
So, Rahmyun? I've got eyes, Yakety-myeong.
Very funny, Ickmyung. Ickmyung, Ickmyung, Ickmyung, Ickmyung.
Rahmyon, Rahmyon, Rahmyon, Rahmyon, Rahmyon, Rahmyon, Rahmyon, Rahmyon, Rahmyon.
I'm good, myon. Boomerang, boomerang. Boomerang.
I want to be a boomerang, boomerang, boomerang, boomerang, boomerang, boomerang, boomerang, boomerang...
I'm in Jiffany's Korean class.
Bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread
Bread is bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread, bread...
I'm not sure if there's such a thing as potato salad in Korea.
Kamja kamja kamja potato chips are kamja kamja potato chips are kamja kamja
Camera kamu kamuchi, right?
Oh, I love you, then.
I love you, saraheyo.
Isn't there like a difference between "I love you" and "I love you"? I love you and I love you in Japan.Is there any difference between "I love you" and "I love you"? I love you and I love you in Japan.
They say "I love you" a lot. They say "I love you" like they love you.
Then they want love. Then they don't say "I love you.
There's no "I love you" or "I love you" in Japan.
Aisai ga saraheyo... very, very much... very, very much like...
Isn't it white? White.
Sorry to bother you, White. Did she say she hates me?
Doron.
Do you love it?
I love you.
Good morning?
It's all good mornings.
And good night?
Say good night, or good night, or good night, or good night.
Charuja.
White.
Say white.
White!
I think Doron is Showa.
That's right.
Die.
Dying.
Look. Isn't it cute?
I thought so.
What's this?
Yes, I thought it was cute. I thought it was cute.
I thought it was a battle cry.
But it's cute. I thought it was different.
I like it.
How do you say "idol"?
Idol.
Thumbnail was cute.
Thank you.
Drink Choaheyo.
He likes it a lot.
That's great.
You remember everything.
I'm learning.
That's why you're so smart.
You're smart.
That's right.
Mie, I'm sitting on top of you in second grade. You're so good.
Elephant.
Elephant. Per!
I'm from Thailand. It's an elephant.
Is it from Thailand?
Yes, from Thailand.
It's very light.
Do you have Korean games? Because I've never thought about it.
I never thought about it.
I thought about it.
That's great. But it's not that easy to decide.
Kim Heenan.
Kim Hinano.
I get the feeling that Kim would have to be pretty good at Korean to get used to it.
Hinyoung.
Kitamy.
Kita.
Hibon.
You said that at one point.
I really like Haemon-chan.
There is an idol girl named Haemon-chan,
When I acted for a while, I didn't use my own name,
Like Hibon.
Haemon! I used to annoy him.
I used to annoy her.
Nico Nico.
Tiffany looks like she's in the Care Cop group.
Tiffany, I bet your butt bone hurts.
No, she looks fine. Tiffany is my
Tiffany is my other name, my real name.
Akemi Kaneshiro, Akemi. Akemi.
Akemi, Akemi, Akemi. You don't know that. You're lucky.
Lucky is her real name, but sometimes she changes her name to Akemi Kaneshiro.
Miu has all the games.
Ninya has a middle name, Tiffany.
I have a middle name, Tiffany.
Yes, that's why you sent me Tiffany, and Mon-chan was Tiffany too
Yeah, she said congratulations!
Ren-chan sent me Anmiko's line stamp.
I'd like to do it on line. I like you, Anmiko!
I'll give it to you. I like Anmiko.
I wonder what beauty is in Korean.
I wonder what "beautiful" means.
Beautiful!
I studied Korean.
That's true.
It's just something that comes naturally to me from watching TV dramas and idols.
I don't know.
It's a lot of study.
I can't even translate it directly.
I can't really visualize it.
I looked it up.
Hmm?
It's there.Yes, there is.
Yes, there is.
It's hard, isn't it?
There must be
Yes, it is.
I hear that a lot, don't I?
Yes, I know.
Yes, it is.
It's impossible
Stop it.
It's Apple.
Apple.
Chin-cha!
I'm turning 21.
Will you send me a love message?
Love message? In Korean, then.
Japanese, please.
Okay. - Okay.
Let's see...
Chin-cha.
Nomu nomu...
It's in the north.
Did you read my line?
Read it?
He wants everyone to hear it.
I'll read it.
Wasn't it long? No, it's fine.
Don't let him win.
He's always long-winded.
But I'm looking forward to it.
His own.
Yes.
Yes, sir. It's 10:05 in person.
Here's the news.
Happy birthday to you today.
That's great.
Thank you for always taking care of me.
I hope you continue to take care of me.
Thank you for everything.
Please continue to take care of me.
Nyan pero nyan pero annyon choo choo saran heyo.
Well then, Saran heyo.
Mashisso mashisso.
Thank you.
Why are you replying to this?
I'm sorry.
I lost my temper.
Sorry.
Here.
I was having a conversation with Miu,
And in reply,
I was sending him a message saying, "You did it, you did it, you did it, you did it, you did it,
I ignored the record.
But he got mad at me.
Sorry.
Looking forward to your reply.
I'll do it now.
I'll do it now. Wish.
Okay, I'll do it.
Okay, you've done it, Teleco.
Thank you.
I'll send you a sorry telecoat.
See you later. I'll wait for your reply.
Okay.
Let's see, now that I'm the president, I can tell you about this tour,
I've been behind Rine since we met that day, right?
And every time I did that, I would... well... I'd take Rine out.
And eat,
And become a beauty.
That's right. You knew she was eating something, right?
She would stop halfway through, right? So I couldn't see your reaction after you stopped,
Why did you stop in the middle? I thought, "Why did you stop in the middle?
Why can't I do it after that?
So I did it, and I did it like this.
Okay.
How's it going? Beauty?
It's done. Let me see you.
Let me see you.
I ate.
Drone!
Can I have a little cutch of mine?
Here, you can borrow this.
I'll put this on.
Meacher, I got called away for a minute.
Here, let me borrow this.
How's that?
How's it going?
I've been to a lot of shows.
I see a lot of eye contact with Mr. Penji.
Lately, I've been flying around on tour.
And when we were on the plane...
I watch a Disney movie and it's right on time.
It's perfect for me.
So...
Baymax.
Yuna said it's her favorite English movie.
She recommended Baymax.I saw Baymax because it was recommended to me.
Baymax.
You know how when you do the "goo-touch" thing, you do the "parala-la-la-la" thing?
Fuji and I have been having a lot of fun lately.
I'll go with you when we're in Cantonation.
Even when we're going with the flow, we just go with the flow...
I'm having fun, maybe next time it will be different
Ine and Mioshi may have noticed, but
But the rest of you...
I just found out the truth.
I was just having fun.
Just like that.
What a gorgeous thing to put two of these on.
I'm always looking at you two over there.
I'm 21 years old.
I just found out.
Thank you for your hard work.
He said he's curious about the little bit of free originality that goes into each duo.
It's true, I don't know what the other members are doing.
Do you see the dancers in the dance?
Mr. Trofs moves around quite freely.
But there are nine of us, so there's a lot going on.
That's why you don't know what's going on.
There's a lot going on on stage that you don't know about.
That's right.
So, you know, we want nine.
Thank you for watching.
Man-chan, you always get me into trouble.
But you're coming.
Yeah, it's fun.
Which side of the argument are you coming from?
Your side.
In the morning...
You know what?
I sent you a congratulations.
I was going to respond to the "thank you" after you left.
I was going to send you something.
I overslept.
I don't know.
Thank you.
You said Tiffany.
Yeah, it's...
That's nice.
Hey, you know what? It is.
Hey, I know. I know.
I thought it was cute.
It just came out.
Mon-san said Tiffany.
She got it for me.
It's like, "Tiffany's.
And electricity.
You have an electric name, don't you?
Appliance name
Tiffany and Co.
Card.
brand? Tiffany brand?
Tiffany & Co.
I'm in trouble.
Not Tiffanys. Tiffanys.
Yes, Tiffanys.
Understood?
Don't repeat.
Tiffany.
Congratulations, Tiffany.
Thank you. Can you give me a message of love?
In small sentences, in Japanese.
Don't be troubled
I love you
I love you too
You guys don't seem to understand Japanese.
My sister, you know, she forgot to say "Yuu"...
I forgot how many shows, how many shows...
When Hina lifted her bangs...
I asked my sister to lift her bangs.
I wonder... when Rinne got bangs, too.
That was, um, Hiroshima?
Part of Hiroshima.
Wow, you have fans.
That's a big fan, isn't it?
There it is.
Hiroshima.
Rinne gave me a haircut first.
She did, didn't she?
Rinne-chan can give you bangs no matter how short they are.
I'm Tiffany with bangs.
Tiffany bangs. That's right.
Nothing is impossible for me.
That was great. You did a good job.
It's a bit of a mess, but I did my best.
It went up so high.
You were so cool.
You're a genius.
I'm glad you told me that Man-chan's bangs were effective.
You looked so mature then.
Really?
Tiffany Power
Spipe.
You're welcome.
Sometimes I do things like that.
I've been watching the comments on this.I saw your comment on this.
Thanks for watching!
I always look forward to your insta posts, Mirei.
I'm going insta-live for the first time in my life today.
Yay!
Celebrating with our 20+ year old members!
That's right, Tork-chan!
Shinshin is turning 20 in a little while, so I'd like to do something like that on Talk-chan.
How about it?
What do you think?
I don't know, I'm just saying. Oh, yeah, inline-inline-yay, it's my first time.
Will you watch it?
Please invite all your friends to come and watch, and make my birthday a big one!
I was tiny... and now I'm 21... and when I say tiny, I mean I was big... and I was tall... and I was a pro.
I was a pro.
I pretended to drink alcohol, but I drank non-alcoholic beverages.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I'd like to try it with the captain... and the six of us.
When I said I'd like to try it, Pearl was all excited and said it'd be great
Thank you for watching!
It's the captain's turn.
That's right.
Did I look like him? Did I look like him? She moves like that, doesn't she?
Pearl moves like this, right? It's like a yay.
Sometimes it's like they're broken.
I'm imitating Pearl.
I've always been clumsy at worst, and mature at best.
I've told you this before.
I've always had a face that doesn't look like a child.
It doesn't change at all from the beginning.
That's why.
It's not so easy to wipe off as an adult.
Do you know what I mean?
Thank you for watching.
You know what I mean?
You know what I mean? Doesn't he look the same?
You don't buy it, do you?
I haven't bought since I was really little.
I know, I know.
So I just realized that it's been 13 minutes.
We're going to be doing a showroom later today, and then we're going to be doing a showroom for about a half hour, and then we're going to do our first in-live show.
I'm gonna do an in-live for the first time in my life, and I'm gonna do an insta-live.
I think I'm going to change my hair.
So I'm going to do a little bit of a photo shoot, okay?
Let's pose!
I don't know how to do stacomime.
I want to do it. I really want to do it.
You've got Mr. Fujitani, one of our seniors, right?
Mr. Fujitani.
I was thinking of asking you to teach me when you have time.
But I haven't had a chance to do so.
I had to give up this time.
Wink with a heart
Hard heart
You're looking for a good angle, aren't you?
Pose with the head in the air
It's hard.
I'm looking for a good angle.
A little bit, no
No leaks today.
It's no good.
There are days like that.
That's life.
I've never really done the bear pose.
I think I'll try this one.
Camera here.
Okay, then.
I guess that's about it.
A few more minutes.
We started at 57 and a half minutes.
You can't get in the gym and come down.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
That's...
It's an abuse load.
Oh, God.
So, I guess I'll wrap it up for now.
Today, May 28th, I celebrate my 21st birthday.
And to commemorate it...
Today, we're going to have a distribution party, and after that, we're going to have a talk show.
I hope you'll continue to watch the talk show afterwards.
Thank you so much for all the congratulations!
So I'll see you soon. Bye bye.
But I don't know how to turn it off.